Daniel
Don't you think
my skills are worthless
Then I'll use those skills
to raise these forest frogs
And I'll pay you back
for every insult you gave me
James, it's Lewes
Do you have any cash
Lend me twenty thousand
- Uncle
- Yes, emergency
Can you lend me twenty thousand
I've spent all my savings
and borrowed from everyone I could
I must succeed this time
I can't afford to fail
To ensure high-quality oil
you need enough water
and good water quality
Plus my special feed
mealworms
Lewes
I heard you're not working for Daniel
and rented a place to raise frogs yourself
Isn't that ridiculous
Do you even know how
Don't lose your parents' life savings
Lewes
Raising forest frogs isn't easy
One mistake
and you'll lose everything
Better to stay with your brother-in-law
It's a steady paycheck
I heard Daniel
made three million this time
How much is he paying you
Brother-in-law
I heard you rented
the greenhouse across the way
Are you crazy
I gave you fifty thousand
was for you and Cynthia to live a good life
not to throw it down the drain
Fifty thousand
The Liu family
has a real spendthrift now
Daniel made a fortune
and cared for his sister
but this loser is wasting it all
For Cynthia to be with him
is the worst luck ever
If I lose, I'll take it
Lewes, are you stupid
50,000, not 500
You're a grown man
How are you less mature than Daniel
No wonder he's getting rich
It's just small change
I'm hatching five times the tadpoles this time
Once they mature
I'll have millions coming in
Lewes
When you're too broke to eat
you can still come work for me
Daniel is so generous
Unlike some people
who get jealous of others' success
I'll raise the best frogs ever
When that time comes
no one will dare look down on me
The quality of the oil
is everything
One degree difference in temperature
and the oil quality drops a level
One missing ingredient in the feed
and the yield drops by ten percent
Daniel
You think it's just throwing them into the water
Without my expertise
those frogs of yours
won't sell for a penny